

262.993.0947 becktj07@uww.edu

becktj07.github.io

Web Developer located in Milwaukee, WI with a demonstrated history of 5+ years working in the digital space. Skilled in Email and Front-end Development (CSS, SCSS, JS Frameworks). Working towards a full-stack role focused on C#. Strong engineering professional with a B.A. Art focused in Graphic Design from UW-Whitewater.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Laughlin Constable

Software Engineer - FE

I worked mainly on Kentico CMS based sites, **NationalMSSociety.org** and **Laughlin.com**. I also did maintenance on Masterlock.com, a custom Java based site, and built emails for various clients. Notable work includes a landing page for MS, https://www.nationalmssociety.org/climb-to-the-top.

Milwaukee, WI December 2019 - September 2020

### **Bader-Rutter**

Jr. Developer

I started as a dedicated email developer for Corteva Agriscience and Zoetis. I worked on landing pages in Oracle's Eloqua platform, and on two large .NET based websites, **Mycogen.com** and **Phytogen.com** respectively.

Milwaukee, WI April 2018 - December 2019

#### **MATC Milwaukee**

Student

Milwaukee, WI Jaunary 2018 - May 2018

After an extended job search, I went back to school full-time. I focused on server-side development with C#. Courses included:

Intro C#, SQL Server, Intermediate C# and .NET Core w/ Entity Framework

Milwaukee, WI October 2014 - August 2017

# Ascedia

Associate Interface Developer

I collaborated with application developers and designers, and brought static design concepts to reality. Client work ranged from large scale, custom builds, to maintenance tasks in versions of Kentico CMS and Wordpress.

### Notable Work:

- Milwaukee County Transit System www.ridemcts.com
- Cubic Designs www.cubicdesigns.com
- Davalid Ridge Hop Farm www.davaliridge.com
- Untitled Creative Studio www.untitledcreativestudio.com

## The LANG Companies

Web Designer

I designed and coded html emails, managed email campaigns, and in-house front end development. I managed product pages and web content for www.lang.com, a site built on Magento e-commerce CMS.

Pewaukee, WI August 2013 - Oct 2014

### **EDUCATION**

University of Wisconsin-Whitewater Mukwonago High School

BA Art - Graphic Design Cum Laude, May 2013 Class of 2008